[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Were you surprised?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "I was a little bit, but over the years of growing up with him it almost seemed like eventually he would do something like this, but not to this magnitude.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "You called him Brandon, not Michael, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brandon", "Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What was he like as a kid, and when did things started to go wrong for him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "NNS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "He was like any other kid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "He'd set the fire up to put the house ablaze?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "At that point we didn't know it was him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "We didn't find out it was him until about 5:00, 6:00 a.m. in the morning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "He also stood over your parents holding an ax.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["6:00 a.m."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Because he was threatening to use them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "He didn't threaten to use them, it's just after they -- after my mom woke up with him standing over her with a butcher knife, it just changed from there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "How did that make you feel as his brother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "I honestly had no words for it, except fear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Did you think he meant it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Do you feel angry that the system betrayed your family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "I'm not angry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Are you grateful to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Yes --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "A guess?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Too many to count.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", ":"], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Do you have any idea where he would have got that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "My opinion on that, he had to get it off the street, and there --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "WDT", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "And is that because there is just too many guns in circulation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "It's not even that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RBR", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What is it that can be done to try and stop more of them doing this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "They need to be looked at more closely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "As a family did you feel in the end -- you had nothing else you could do, that it was a helpless situation for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Towards the end before I stopped really talking to him, I felt hopeless at helping him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "The shooting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Do you want to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Right now I'm honestly not sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "What do you think will happen to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "I couldn't tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "And nothing happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What would you say to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "He just wanted to let me know that him and his wife and his family was very proud of what I did and everybody wanted to thank me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "What did you think of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, certainly, it's a very troubling statements that his brother indicated to us here on television.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What did you think about her actions, particularly when you heard that 911 call which really has inspired everybody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "What we have seen in the last few days is what I get to see every day as principal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Dr. Bolden, do you have any idea what her news was that was so devastating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Not at all and she has the ability to absorb issues that impact her life, and it never perfect -- it never really inhibits her ability to be professional and do what she needs to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Bolden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "As a police officer, what did you think of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well, I think there's something to be learned certainly from the actions that she took that day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What is your quick reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Well, you know, I think the thing -- you know, we got to think that through a lot more in this country in terms whether teachers should be armed or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Would you like to see your teachers armed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "That's a question that's always been debatable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "What's missing in this story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "They do it every time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "WP", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Is it because two of the three alleged killers here were black, therefore it must be a race crime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "We found from some of these tweets which was that he said he didn't like white people and he was planning on going out and killing people, and that would be what many would say is a hate crime.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 295, "question": "So how does that work with your this is a one-race gang?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I just said -- I just said --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Right, but well -- yes, but is there actual evidence that he set out deliberately to kill a white person?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "RB", ":", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "I think there is a lot of evidence if you look at what he said in his own words online --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Glenn Beck"]}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, first, the idea that the media does not include people like Glenn Beck is ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "I'm going to respond, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Please do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "You know what I think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Let me finish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "You didn't like the police and how they investigated it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "How are you coping as a family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, it's very hard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah"]}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "How are they coping do you think after this appalling ordeal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Well, Hannah is trying to be strong because that's what she would do for her mother and that's the way her mother kind of raised her to be strong like she was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Did you know this man, James DiMaggio, the kidnapper and the man we believe is responsible for killing Christina and Ethan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I've met him a couple of times but I didn't really know him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James DiMaggio", "Christina", "Ethan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Can you quite believe what has happened here and do you fully understand yet what has happened here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "I don't think it's actually set in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "What do you think has been behind all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "You know, I have no idea exactly what he had been thinking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Do you believe that could possibly be true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Why do you think those rumors have been circulating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I believe it's his sister starting these rumors because of this insurance thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "How are you all going to deal with that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I'm not quite sure yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think they are going through the natural process of grief and it's -- as I've been saying all along that at some point there's going to be a need for the family to understand what motivated Jim to do these atrocious acts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim"], "LOCATION": ["Laura"]}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Are you able to shed any more light on all these wild rumors about some relationship between James DiMaggio and Christina, Hannah's mother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "The original stories came to Laura from neighbors in the area that they had believe that Jim had possibly had a relationship with her, and that's where, you know, she got all worried and scared and confused and she's, you know, going through the same grieving process and -- as they are.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James DiMaggio", "Christina", "Hannah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wendy Davis"], "LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Who have you got emerging as winners of the summer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Wendy Davis, who was the woman who did the filibuster in Texas.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Who else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "And she spoke her mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last year"]}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Are you a -- are you a big fan of the -- was the royal baby a winner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "The royal baby is a winner in the sense that the royal baby got actually more focus from the American people than they've done on anything else in the last year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Winners or losers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "A-Rod is, you know, it's really good to make sure that children are becoming ambivalent about sports, so that they can watch and go, wow, I need him to hit a homerun, but he's done steroids and he's kind of creepy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]